## Justin Jones Hudsonville, MI 49426

Email: <u>Jeo961@gmail.com</u> Github: <u>JustinJonesGC</u>
Phone: 616-322-0988 Linkedin: <u>justinjones-961</u>

I graduated from GRCC with an Associates in Computer Science in 2018. I worked as a Visual Basic Programmer at Structural Concepts. While I was there, I created multiple programs that would sort large amounts of information. These programs would display a user interface where they can select which parts and colors they need and it would retrieve all related info. I've also worked as a Teaching Assistant at Grand Circus where I help people learn front-end and back-end skills and start a career as a developer. I'm looking forward to working full time as a developer on a software team.

## Education

• Associate's Degree, Computer Science

Grand Rapids Community College, August 2016 - May 2018

Unreal Engine Developer

Udemy April 2020 - Current

## **Technical Skills**

- Angularjs
- API
- C#
- C# .Net
- C++
- Git/Github

- Html/Css
- Java
- Javascript
- JSON
- TDD
- SQL

- Visual Basic
- VBA
- XAML
- XML

## **Work Experience**

Visual Basic Programmer | Structural Concepts

9/23/2019- 2/12/2020

- Created programs to sort large amounts of information and to only retrieve relevant info based on user input.
- Maintained older programs based on user feedback.
- Updated older programs to match the current revisions of the related data.
- Created a user interface to allow for a simpler user experience while the program handles the complex tasks behind the scenes.

Teaching Assistant | Grand Circus, Grand Rapids

4/16/2018 - 7/28/2019

- Taught and supported 50 new programming students over 5 front-end and back-end coding bootcamps; helped achieve 82% graduate rate.
- Expanded and improved the curriculum in meaningful ways, including
  - Created new front-end and back-end exercises to provide additional support to students based on their individual needs
  - Updated curriculum slides to explain complex concepts more clearly
- Taught free Intro to Coding Workshops to help the public learn coding fundamentals and take their first steps in the field.